I said even the eagle in
the sky cannot sense me.
You didn't find us, I turned
your best one to a bait.
I lured the wolf into the trap.
We have not lost our minds to hold...
...the hand of friendship you extended...
What kind of dog are you that...
..you attack my castles..
...where you came as a guest? You came and...
...abducted my Shahzade and my Bey.
What kind of dog are you?
While sharing my meal...
...you tried to poison the people.
Traitor, treacherous, jackal,
you call these names to us.
But you call yourselves glorious, brave and...
..powerful.
Is that so, Osman? -Right...
Of course.
The reputation and honor of a valiant...
...come from the path they walk.
But for people like you..
...your path is only arrogance and heedlessness.
Ah, your arrogance...
It's this arrogance that
has brought you to this state.
Faithless dog.
You will get even more pale.
The poison running in your blood...
...will break your legs.
You will kneel before me, Osman.
You will kneel.
My Fatma..
My beautiful daughter.
Mother..
Did my brother..
...come?
He will come, my daughter.
He will come, don't worry.
Cover yourself. Come on.
-Mother...
Mother don't leave...
Meryem...
You say "mother" in such a way that Meryem...
...your voice puts out the old fire in me.
Your face, your eyes...
It's like a dream.
I feel like my daughter who will
never grow up is right next to me.
You have a fever.
Mine was just a dream..
You are someone else's wounded bird.
I am here to protect you...
...but I cannot do anything.
My Allah, give us power..
Give us power...
Give us power to resist.
Give us power..
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
My Bey!
I will never fall! Never!
-I will never kneel before the infidel.
-You will!
I said you will!
You will do as I say, or..
...your son Orhan and the
other dog will beg me to kill them.
Never!
I will never kneel!
No one can make me kneel!
Faithless dog!
Look at me!
We did not beg to live, nor did we beg to die.
If we are going to die by the sword
of the infidel, sure we will, but...
Death does not disgrace us.
Never!
But our lands will never face defeat.
They will, Osman
They will.
If you are not going to give up your state
for your own life or for your children,
you will do so for the lives of your people
The poison in your veins is
not only in the wells of your tribe,
but also in Sogut, Mekece,
Akhisar, all your lands.
Only a treacherous being who does not trust
his own strength like you would do this!
As long as your stubbornness
and impertinence continue,
you will not get this antidote
from me and your Hatun
your children, your army, your people
They will die one by one.
What do you want from me?
You will visit everywhere in
your tribe and land with me.
You will bow down to Mongols.
You will surrender, willingly.
And you will let your people
hear that you surrendered.
Mother...
-I am alright. I am alright.
I am alright. I am...
I am alright.
Mother, you are ill. You need to take a rest.
You are getting weaker.
-I am alright.
How is the situation, my son?
Couldn't you find the antidote?
They are all in a fever.
The news is not good, mother.
Not just the tribe...
People started to
show the effects of the
poisoning in Sogut,
Yenisehir and in all our lands.
They poisoned them as well.
What are you saying, Alaeddin?
We need a solution, Alaeddin.
What about Osman?
The enemies have the antidote.
The elderly and children are the most affected.
But...
...Alps are also losing their power, mother.
We are losing our strength.
It's such a poison that...
...it kills people from the inside slowly.
I can slow its effect.
But I cannot cure it, mother.
We will not give up, my son.
I will stand tall until you find the antidote.
We will find it.
-We will find it, my son.
-God willing, mother.
Mother... Mother, don't leave.
If she were alive
...Halime would be at this age now.
Let me see your face once, mother.
It's all dark, mother.
It's all dark.
Bala Hatun.
You don't look well.
I got some healing herbs boiled. Drink.
No!
Don't drink anything she gives, mother.
She may harm you.
-We can't trust Begum Hatun.
-What are you talking about, Gonca?
You know me well.
And those who know me know this.
As long as I keep breathing,
I and the men following me will never stop...
...before we take revenge
from you and people like you.
Even in this situation
...you still keep being arrogant.
What you call arrogance is my honor and glory.
It's what you lack.
You have only arrogance and failure.
-It's easy to kill you.
Stay away from my Bey, you dog
You made up a cause and spread it in the hearts.
Yet I will take it off from the hearts.
It's easy to die.
But I will make you and your
nation slaves of Mongolians.
Turks...
...neither kneel..
...nor serve the servants!
You and your nation...
...will be whatever I desire.
Nokers (Mongolian Soldier), take the cage.
Stop!
Go to your tribe and see!
See and kneel before me..
...to save your people
I will be your death.
I will be your butcher.
You can't run off, Osman.
You can't run off.
Even if you run away from
this, you can't escape your fate.
Tell me what's going on.
Gonca is angry with me. She
doesn't know what she says..
Shut up, Begum!
You can't deceive me.
Your aide Guldane confessed
everything before she died.
She confessed what, Gonca?
All the evil actions in the tribe
were performed by Begum.
It was her who turned us against
each other and made evil plans.
We protected you.
We looked after you and gave you duties.
Why did you do that, Begum?
-It's a slander.
-I'm not done yet, Begum.
Because she wants to put you in trouble, mother.
Because Begum Hatun...
...loves Osman Bey.
Is this how you return my favors, Gonca?
Favors?
You didn't do me favors, Begum.
You just cared about yourself.
You wanted to make me turn against my family.
In fact, your biggest purpose
was to hurt my mother, right?
You were going to hit me
through my children, huh?
I told you before.
I told you that your undue
bravery would cost your life.
I didn't make a mistake.
I fell in love with Osman Bey long before you.
Love?
Love, huh?
What do you know about love?
Osman Bey is my love.
Yours is just a dark stain.
There is no place for that stain, Begum.
You can't dishonor love
with your poisonous tongue.
You're confused...
..about love.
You thought it was
ambition... Such an ambition...
...that the fire burned the whole tribe.
What do you mean?
Everyone is poisoned, Begum.
And why are you not?
You blame me for this too?
You're looking for one to execute.
My only mistake was falling in love.
-Enough!
Pack up your things and leave this tribe.
I don't want you here. You have to leave.
You can't kick me out.
As long as Osman Bey doesn't kick me out,
I am not going anywhere!
What, Bala?
Are you not confident?
Are you afraid of me?
Afraid, huh?
You can't scare me, Begum.
Either you will go yourself...
...or I know how to kick you out.
Even if everybody obeys
you in this tribe, I won't.
And I'm not going anywhere just
because you're telling me to leave.
Osman Bey invited me to this tribe.
I won't go anywhere without his order.
Don't you mention my
husband's name again, hatun.
I said what I said.
Next time, my sword will speak.
Get out of my sight!
Mother.
You're good.
-My Bey.
-Warriors.
-Thanks to Allah.
We were looking for you, my Bey.
Orhan Bey and Boran Bey.
-Any news?
-We looked everywhere and followed every trail.
But we couldn't find.
We left the alps who were in bad
condition in a tribe nearby, my Bey.
But all the tribes have the same problem.
They poisoned all the water.
People are sick.
They're dying, my Bey.
Inform all the healers
in all of our lands, Aykurt.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Here we go.
People shouldn't fall weaker.
-We're going to our tribe.
-My Bey.
Will we stop looking for
Shahzade Orhan and Boran Bey?
The owl called Ulugan...
...can't harm my son or
Boran without my knowledge.
Don't worry.
We're going to our tribe.
Come on!
Orhan.
I was just with your father.
You should know your life
doesn't matter at all to him.
What are you talking about, dog?
Kill me if you desire.
Stop playing game like kids!
Your father spoke the same.
All his people are about to die of poison.
But he still keeps his tail upright.
This arrogance of yours will destroy you.
You're going to die because of your father.
Whatever my father does
...he does the best.
I'd sacrifice myself even
if I had a thousand lives!
But you should know this, dog.
We weren't born to be captives.
Neither my father nor I will ever...
...kneel before a dog like you.
He thinks we are like Candar and Germiyan...
...who he made kneel and bow, my Shahzade.
But he doesn't know.
We vowed to spread...
...the ideal of Turks in the world.
What can death even do to us?
Do whatever you can, dastard.
I will destroy your culture.
I will crush your ideals!
Osman will fall...
...and you will vanish.
Then...
...he will bow before me like a dog.
Untie him.
Let's see if his feet are
as strong as his tongue.
My Shahzade... My Shahzade!
You dastards.
You dastards!
Fight like a man! My Shahzade!
You will die slowly, Orhan.
My nokers(Mongolian Soldier) will have a feast.
They will stand against you and drink kimiz.
Get him up.
I bear witness that
there is no god but Allah...
You won't die right away.
Pour the oil.
You dastards! You dogs!
I will pour that oil on you as well.
Wait...
Kiliz!
I bear witness that there is no deity but, Allah,
and I bear witness that Muhammad is th...
You will pay the price
of this slap heavily, Bala.
I swear...
You'll wish you were dead!
You too, Gonca. You too.
I did a favour to you, I protected you!
But you let me down!
And you thought I brought the poison, huh?
Ilbay...
I went to the well... Here, drink clean water.
Thank you.
Ayse was not poisoned...
I was also not poisoned...
Did you know it?
Ilbay, did you know about the poison?
Begum is blinded by her ambition.
We need to take measures.
She won't be able to hurt us a bit.
Mother...
Mother, are you alright? You don't seem alright.
-I am alright.
I am alright.
Are you alright?
Did you visit a healer?
-A healer?
Something is different...
Mother...
I wanted to tell this to Orhan first, but...
...I am pregnant.
My daughter...
After all these problems... May it be blessed.
Thanks to Allah..
May Allah let it grow up
with its father and mother.
Mother...
Orhan will come back, right?
God willing, he will come back, my daughter.
He will come back.
-God willing.
-God willing...
...you will have the baby safe and sound...
...with Orhan Bey, Holofira.
Hug now, huh?
What did I tell you?
You are the mountains behind my sons.
You cannot be separated.
Come on, my daughters.
Come on.
Osman Bey is here. -Orhan!
Come on... Come on..
Osman Bey... My child..
She has a high temperature. Give her to me...
Come here, my dear.
My Bey... Don't go in. The
people inside are not well.
Please find a cure.
My Bey...
Find a cure.
For Allah's sake save us.
Save us from this disease.
Orhan...
Mother...
Orhan is not there!
Mother, Orhan...
Stop, wait, my daughter. Calm down.
Come. Come.
My Bey, are you alright?
I'm alright.
Is there any news from Orhan or Boran?
No. Not yet.
But we'll find them.
Father..
You are not alright.
You have a fever.
Alaeddin... What did you do?
Could you find a way to cure this?
I couldn't, my Bey.
Wherever they brought this disease...
...the effect of the poison is very severe.
But we were able to break its effect a little.
Alps can resist but...
...the elderly and the children cannot, my Bey.
It kills them one by one.
Do your best...
...and find something.
I will try finding a way, father...
Cerkutay Bey.
You know the Mongols.
They won't do something bad to Orhan, right?
They won't kill him, right?
...don't know, Holofira Hatun.
But..
...there is one thing I know. My Shahzade...
...is strong.
My Shahzade is powerful. He won't fall down.
My daughter...
Stand tall.
They cannot do anything to Orhan...
My daughter... my daughter...
-Holofira.. -Bring some water!
What is happening? -Come on!
Take her, she will have
some rest. Come on, take her!
What happened to her?
Among all these bad things...
...hope found us.
Holofira is pregnant.
Orhan will be a father, God willing.
Your state will have a grandchild.
What are you doing here?
I brought you a gift, Ulugan.
A gift for you and
your nokers (Mongolian Soldier).
I did not come here for gold.
I came here to shed blood.
What do you want, Red Hatun?
Just...
I want an antidote for one person.
Don't worry.
Your spy will live.
Osman will bow down to me tomorrow.
And he will take the antidote.
What if the opposite happens?
Then..
..your friend will die.
Ulugan.
You wanted me to give Osman to you.
You cannot stop me.
Thus, we came to you with an agreement.
I never make agreements.
And I punish those who threaten me.
I am not afraid of death, Ulugan.
I will take back the castles that Osman
took from me, one way or another.
Everything Osman has...
...is mine now.
If you draw your sword,
that means we'll be in war.
Gladly.
I will gladly fight against you.
But Osman makes his plans like a wolf.
If you fall, no one will be standing behind you.
The enemies of our enemies are our friends.
Lukas.
Ulugan
We don't want to
be enemies with you.
On the contrary...
..we want to unite..
...and drink kimiz(Turkic-Mongolic drink) together.
I am impressed.
Red Hatun.
If you need help for Osman, we'll be here.
I hope we are on the same side.
Mother...
My daughter.
Father...
Are you here? -I am..
My brother...
Did my brother come with you?
Your brother will come.
He will come.
My brother...
...will come together with his baby...
...right, father? It won't
die this time, right, father?
We will not die, right?
No, my daughter...Don't worry.
Your brother will come back.
We will be a big family again, huh?
We will find the shifa.
Halime...
Halime is gone..
My brother...
If we lose my brother as well..
Look, Halime was little...
Your brother is strong. Nothing will
happen to him. He will come back.
He will come back.
Come on. Have some rest.
Aunt..
Aunt...
Aunt, don't go... It's too cold...
Ah my beautiful daughter...
Her fever did not go down.
What are we going to do?
Our children are burning in front of us.
Does she have an aunt?
She never told me.
I heard it for the first time.
We did not have any
room left in the healing tent.
And we placed her here.
You did well. You did well...
She has...
...something that puts out the fire in my heart.
My Bala, you are not alright.
Come on, have some rest, my Bala.
I'll have some rest, but what about you?
This poison on one side...
...our child Orhan, our
companion Boran on the other...
My Bala, as you, my
people, my tribe feel better...
..I feel better.
Your breath and hearts give me strength.
Come on.
Now you will go and rest.
And you will get up stronger. Come on.
We'll wake up together tomorrow.
Good...
Father...
Father... father don't leave!
It's too dark...
Father, father don't go!
Father...
-It's too dark.
-You're afraid of dark, huh?
But you have a strong heart.
In your eyes, your voice...
...and in your heart,
there is something familiar.
Allah sent you to me to look after.
You joined our table and
ate our food. Don't worry.
Osman Bey is here for you, girl.
Don't worry.
Osman.
Are you alright?
-Alaaddin!
-Mother.
-Don't worry.
-Check him, son. He's not well.
-Are you alright, father?
-It's fine.
You have a high fever.
-I'm fine.
-In the name of Allah.
Father, drink some.
Drink, father.
It will make you feel better.
Take this.
Well...
I need to go now.
Where are you going at this late hour?
There is a star at every dark night, Bala.
It enlightens our way.
I need to find that star.
Don't carry the burden on your own, Osman.
Let me be with you until you find the star.
You're always with me. You stay here.
You stay.
For my nation and state
...I need to find the light myself.
You carry all the burdens of the
state on your shoulders, my Osman.
May Allah help you.
I'm doing...
...everything to take our right, my girl.
Everything.
Sorry for coming inside...
...without permission, Ilbay.
Do you need something, Begum Hatun?
What's the matter?
Not something bad.
Everybody is poisoned.
But somehow, Ayse isn't infected.
So this is all good to me.
Thanks to Allah.
You didn't drink poisonous water, it seems.
Thanks to you, Ilbay.
But I want to know something.
You are Ilbay, grandson of
Sungur Tegin from Kayi bloodline.
Why did you poison your uncle's
son Osman's tribe and family?
No. You're poisoned Begum Hatun.
-You're delusional.
-Stop it, Ilbay.
I know everything.
I heard you talking to Ayse.
What will happen to you when
I tell Osman Bey what I know?
Can you imagine that?
Why would they believe you?
ULUGAN SECRET PLACE
You're a tough man, Bey's son.
Let's see the limits of your strength.
Do your best, you dog.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldier) , show no mercy!
My Shahzade, hold on! Hold on!
Even if I know it will cost my life, I
will drown you in your blood, dog!
Wait for your turn, you fiery boy.
What I'm going to do to you...
...will make you lose your poor mind.
I'm already mad.
It doesn't matter even if I lose my mind.
I will make your ominous head fall, you dog.
We'll see.
Hold on, my Shahzade. Hold on.
For sure, I'm well trained, Boran Bey.
These jackals are incapable of...
...killing and even tiring me up.
Unable?
-I will show you now!
-Altuga!
Keep your hatred in your heart.
His living body is more valuable.
Yet both your living and
dead body are filthy, Ulugan.
Your life is on the edge of my knife.
If you want your tongue to stay in your
mouth and your head on your shoulders,
...watch your words.
You, untie him.
Go and let Osman know
about his shahzade's situation.
If he kneels, his shahzade will live.
If he makes another mistake
...I will send his bones tomorrow.
Cover his eyes.
We'll take care of you
All of you
My Shahzade, hold on.
We'll come for you. Hold on, my Shahzade!
-Ulugan.
You have hopes in vain.
The arrow you shoot will never hit the target.
I couldn't find out, father.
Whatever I tried didn't work.
I slow it down.
I slow it down but they get
worse again after a while.
If we can't find the antidote
...how long can we survive, son?
Weak ones...
...can't survive, mother.
I don't know.
What will we do, my Bey?
They aren't giving us the antidote.
They'd choke us if they had a chance.
If we surrender
...they'll give the antidote.
Surrender?
They want you, Osman.
No.
We'd rather die than surrender.
If Orhan were here
...he wouldn't want this either, father.
This flag...
This tribe will never surrender.
But...
If people die,
If people die one by one,
...nothing will be left behind.
We sacrificed many lives
for these lands, father.
Again we would. All of us would.
You're right, son.
We sacrificed many lives for these lands.
Of course we would.
But...
Our job...
...is not to die, but make live.
If people are out of breath,
...who will this flag wave for?
If the tribe falls, how will the state rise?
We won't die.
We will make live.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in, Yusuf.
-What's the news?
-My Bey.
Begum Hatun isn't around.
I looked everywhere. Nobody has seen her.
I came here to ask if she had some duty here.
It seems she listened to me.
Bala.
-Do you know?
-I asked her to leave the tribe, my Bey.
A personal matter. I will tell you.
Stop struggling, Begum Hatun.
You forced me to do this.
I won't kill you. Don't be afraid.
I can't kill you.
Well... I can't let you expose me either.
Stop struggling. Nobody can hear you here.
I set the fire. You won't feel cold.
I'm leaving now.
If you calm down by the time I
come back, we will talk nicely.
Maybe we can have a deal, huh?
My Bey, Alaaddin has sent
this. It shall make you feel better.
Bala, you take some too.
You need to regain strength too. Come on.
We have to be strong.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Are you angry that I sent Begum away?
No. You well thought. Well...
For unity and order, there shouldn't
be troublemakers in the tribe.
My Orhan's dream..
..has come true.
He's going to be a father.
He doesn't know, though.
Yes, he's going to be a father.
Orhan is a strong boy. He'll
feel the baby. Don't worry.
What have you decided, my Bey?
You didn't say anything.
Alaaddin is working day and night, but...
...it seems he won't be
able to find the antidote.
I don't care about myself or our children...
But my people, my nation...
Their breath is a heavy burden for me, Bala.
And surrender on the other side...
That's too heavy as well.
Just sending you to them?
Don't say that, Osman.
How can I accept that?
-Bala.
You and I have gone through many tests.
We loved each other which was a test.
We loved our children which was a test.
And now our child and nation...
This is the new test. Don't worry.
We'll get over this too together.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in, Cerkutay.
Boran..
My Bey.
Are you alright?
I'm fine, my Bey. Thank Allah.
I'm fine, but...
My Shahzade...
Orhan Bey is in a terrible situation, my Bey.
My Bey.
If we go there to help him in no time,
May Allah forbid this, but...
...they will kill Orhan Bey.
Orhan...
Father.
Take a deep breath, come on.
Come on.
I've been fighting for years.
I got many wounds.
But I have never seen such a vile and evil plan.
My Allah.
My Allah, You are the one Who protects.
Don't deprive us of your gifts, my Allah.
Aameen.
My Bey.
The situation is worse than yesterday.
We're losing more lives day by day.
My Bey.
A Mongolian commander is here.
Let him come.
Don't spill out hatred against me.
Who did this to you is your Osman Bey.
You're in this condition because
of his arrogance and impertinence.
What do you say, Osman?
Will you be their death?
Have you made up your mind?
Will you bow and kneel?
You won.
If you had given a different response
...I wouldn't wait for the
poison to break your people...
...but paint this square with blood.
Now...
Kneel.
I did this only for my innocent people.
Give me the antidote now.
-I said kneel!
-What are you saying?
Wait. Draw back.
I never kneel.
I said you win.
I surrender now.
So be it.
You surrendered, anyway.
In Sogut, you will bow and kneel before me.
Hand out the antidote now.
Take this to every tribe whose well is poisoned.
Your people are mine, after all.
I don't want them to die.
Shahzade Orhan. Where is he?
We'll release him, Osman. Don't worry.
But there is something you need to do first.
You will visit every land of yours with me.
And tell your people that you
bowed against Mongolians.
Come on! Chain his hands!
Don't touch me!
-Boran..
My Bey...
Make them move.
Father... no! -Father!
Father, no! -Father!
My Alaeddin Bey!
Father! -No! No!
Father, what are you doing? Don't!
Don't!
-Stop! Stop!
Father! Father!
Let me go! Let me go!
No, Alaeddin!
Don't!
Don't! Father! Father!
Let me go!
The boots.
Mother, let me go!
-Alaeddin stop! Stop!
Let me go!
Let me go! -Father! Dastard dog!
I will kill you all!
Alaeddin stop! Stop!
Don't take our Bey!
Don't leave us!
You are trying for no reason, you Altuga dog.
Your torture will only make me stronger.
It will strengthen my faith, you dog.
I heard..
..these words in Samarkand..
...Konya...
...and other Turk lands, Bey's son.
Ask this steel.
What do you say, steel?
Brave hands..
...were broken one by one before
the strength of Mongols, right?
You will also be broken.
The ropes around your wrists...
...will be the halter of your valiants.
With these blazing irons...
...I will strip the skin off the bones of many.
If martyrdom...
...is written in the fate of my valiants...
...they will gladly embrace it.
One of us might die...
...but a thousand will come after him.
For every one of us who falls..
...a thousand will rise.
But your evilness..
...before that evillness of
yours take root in this land...
...your miserable head will be cut off.
Orhan, Orhan.
Even your father Osman became the dog of Ulugan.
Tell me.
Who will cut my head off now?
Even if the Turk is chained, he is still a wolf.
Don't you feel victorious.
There are many valiants...
...who can take your dirty head...
..in our lands.
I will bury those valiants
that you think is many...
...in a single grave, Orhan.
Kayi's dark fate...
...was written when you
let Cerkutay in the tribe...
...who carried Mongol blood.
Now I understand your desire for revenge.
You are mad because Cerkutay chose us...
..and not you.
That's why your heart is in pain.
But, dog...
..you will burn in flames.
There is only one fire that burns in me, Orhan.
The fire of revenge.
That dastard will be crushed under the...
...shoes of my horse like a traitor and die.
The world will see the power of Mongols.
Kayis, Byzantium, all of you.
Everyone will bow down to Mongols.
I know how precious Poena is to you.
But aren't you exaggerating a bit?
You got us into a fight with that dirty Mongol.
I gave years of my life to Poena, Lukas.
And now, when I had
Osman and Bala in my hands...
That damned Mongol...
...ruined all my plans.
Are you angry with Ulugan
because he ruined your plans or...
...because he tried to kill Poena?
What are you trying to say, Lukas?
After Poena ends the Kayis, it will be her turn.
You know that, right?
We cannot let a single Kayi live.
Even if it's Poena.
Sure.
Don't worry.
Sir, Ulugan went to Kayi tribe.
Osman took the antidote
and surrendered to Ulugan.
Good.
This is good news, Hristo.
Gather our army.
They must be ready.
Once Osman falls, we will start from the
borders and take back what is ours, one by one.
Lukas, you heard Ulugan.
Attacking Osman's lands and
making him your enemy is not wise.
Once Osman falls, none
of it will matter anymore.
They will think we are their friends.
But I won't let them keep what is mine, Sofia.
This is the result of his arrogance.
You see the situation of your leader?
Look at him, so you'll learn a lesson.
My Bey...
Father..
I wish my Allah had taken my life..
..so that I wouldn't have to
see my Bey in this state, brother.
I cannot draw my sword..
...and this shame will not leave me forever.
Mother... Mother, we won't let
them take my father, right, mother?
Fatma, your father is doing
everything for our people.
Stand tall, my daughter.
Stand tall.
As I promised, Osman.
Everyone in your tribe is healthy again.
When the antidote reaches them, everyone in
all your lands will be in the same condition.
But this is the end of your state.
As long as their traditions live, a
Turk will never be left without a state.
But we could not teach this to those like you.
I will destroy your traditions as well.
I will make your descendants forget everything
you believe and sacrifice your lives for.
Father! Father!
Father!
Nokers(Mongolian Soldier) will stay in your tribe.
As long as no one causes
trouble, no one's life will be taken.
Come on now.
No!
Father!
My Allah, protect us.
Don't worry.
For sure, they cannot do anything to us!
Move!
Drop it!
Move! Move!
Shut up!
Don't touch my father!
What are you doing?!
Don't touch it!
Don't touch our banner!
Our banner!
Dastard dogs! Dastard dogs!
What did you do to Osman Bey?
Don't hurt the people!
Why do you hurt innocent people?
Don't touch them!
Come! Look at your Bey's face! Come!
Look at Osman Bey!
Open your eyes! Look at him!
Look at your Osman Bey!
Don't touch them!
What do you want from innocent people?
Dastard dog! What do you
want from them? My dear...
Don't worry.
It will be alright.
Don't hurt innocent people!
Look at your Bey!
He is in this situation because
of his ambition and courage!
And you are in this situation
because of his ambition!
You are suffering from diseases.
You have a miserable Bey!
Don't worry...
I will break free from these chains.
Ulugan... Then you will stand before me.
Then we will see..
...if you will get away with this oppression...
Hang on.
Don't touch the banner! No!
No!
O people! Don't worry!
For sure, these days will pass! Allah
is with us, we will not give up hope!
Stop...
Stop!
What happened Osman?
I have to pray.
It's time for prayer.
My Bey...
Shall we lay a hide on
the ground for you as well?
Don't worry...
When we arrive in Sogut...
...you will worship me...
...in front of your people.
From now on, you will
direct all your prayers to me.
I decide..
..if you die or live.
I am the one who is victorious.
There is no Victor except Allah.
I bow to no one except Allah.
Allah is the greatest!
I thought you had calmed down.
But you didn't.
I will open your mouth.
But don't yell.
We need to talk.
Talk about what?
You think I will forget what you did to me?
-Look.
Say thanks first.
You seemed to have manners.
Aren't you afraid that this
will be heard by people?
Afraid of whom?
Osman?
Osman's finished, Begum Hatun.
Mongolians got him. The tribe has no head.
My time has come.
The reign of Ilbay Bey,
grandson of Sungur Tegin.
What did Osman Bey do
to you and you're so hateful?
What did he do?
By making use of my
grandfather Sungur Tegin's legacy,
...he established a state for himself.
Now I will take back the
legacy that was my right.
What do you want from me?
You should know this first.
I won't harm you.
Until I sit on the chair
...I will do my best to stop you
from telling the others what you know.
You will wait here.
-Then what?
-You will stand beside me.
Maybe.
Always.
We can get married.
No?
You think I will say yes just
because you have the chair?
You will, Begum Hatun. You will.
The ambition and desire for power...
...in your beautiful eyes
will make you say that.
Don't be stubborn now. You must be hungry.
Nobody can hold me by force!
Although you're blinded by your
anger, you are a smart woman.
And also strong.
You and I won't rule only the frontiers...
...but the whole world, Begum Hatun.
Osman Bey! Osman Bey!
Release my Bey, dastards!
O people of Sogut!
Don't be worrying.
For sure, we will be alright.
Untie him and get him down.
Release Osman Bey!
Osman Bey!
My Bey!
Release Osman Bey!
Osman, stand up.
Leave him.
You disbeliever dog!
What have they done to you, my Bey.
My boy.
-Are you alright.
-I'm fine.
Don't worry.
We'll be good.
We'll be good. All good.
Go to your mother now.
Come on.
Let me kiss you.
You devil's dog.
Get your hands off!
The courage that child takes from your eyes...
There will be sign of it soon.
You will fall off even that child's eyes.
In the hearts of those
children, there is endless faith.
It's the faith that will
destroy people like you.
Walk like this...
...before your people
in the streets of this city.
Then we will see if they have
any faith left in their hearts.
Take him.
Release Osman Bey!
Don't worry!
O people
We won't give up! We won't collapse!
Where are they taking you, my Bey?
-We won't give up.
Don't worry! Stop harming people!
Don't harm people!
Don't worry, my people!
Allah's willing! Allah's willing!
Allah's willing!
Don't worry.
O people of Sogut!
Our state will never collapse!
Allah is the greatest!
You're done, Orhan. You
will take your last breath now.
Commander Ulugan got Osman, Altuga.
-My Bey...
Did you hear, Orhan?
Your father knelt before us. But he's too late.
You're out of life.
We will throw your dead
body at your father's feet.
One day... You will pay for what you did.
One day.
Nobody can beat us, Orhan.
It's time for you to die.
I'm here, brother!
-Alps, attack!
-I'm here for you, brother.
Come here!
I'm here, brother!
I'm here, brother.
What have they done to you, brother?
Nobody can harm me as long
as I have a brother like you.
Alaaddin.
-Altuga.
-Yes, Altuga.
I will be your death, brother.
Now you will use your weapons..
...and end your life that you
have led like a traitor. Come on!
You were like this before too.
If Balgay hadn't taken you with
him, you'd have lived like a coward.
You were always weak, brother.
You're still weak. Come on.
Come on, attack me.
Don't make me kill my own brother, Altuga.
Yours isn't the right path.
Leave that path.
I'd rather die than be a
traitor of Mongolians like you.
Alaaddin, how are the people in our tribe doing?
I will tell you, brother.
I will tell you something.
Come, come.
Alaaddin, bad news or good news?
Come on, brother.
It's good news.
You'll see when you go there.
Behind you, Alaaddin!
Let's go, brother! My brave brother!
Let's go.
Brother!
The worst day of Kayis!
-See, Osman?
-Stop this cruelty!
Your people's tears.
The filth in their hearts...
...is flowing out due to their respect for you.
See where arrogance ends up?
What you call forced respect is the filth.
You will never know what true respect is.
You disbeliever dog!
You're here, huh?
I didn't want to miss the
show, Commander Ulugan.
Thanks for the invitation.
With our power, we again united
all the heathens against us, huh?
Thank Allah.
Power, huh?
You're arrogant even in chains, Osman.
I'd prefer to kill you myself, but...
...seeing you like this...
...is priceless.
Come, come to me.
Bring Osman.
He has things to tell his people.
Get off your hands!
-I will...
-Lighten up, Sofia.
Your little angel is fine.
Seeing Osman like this...
We couldn't imagine this much.
It's not enough that Osman
and Bala will live with this shame.
If not today, tomorrow.
If not by Ulugan, they will...
...be killed by me.
Allah is the greatest!
Your nokers (Mongolian Soldier) are dead.
Surrender to Osman Bey's justice.
Osman Bey, huh?
You can't give me orders, Cerkutay.
You can't give me orders. I will never give up.
Ever!
We will never die before we wipe you off!
Allah is the greatest!
Last warning. Drop your dagger.
Surrender.
I never bow, Cerkutay.
You know me. Never.
You're still weak, Cerkutay.
Still.
Is everyone alright?
-My Bey..
-Alaeddin...
Tell me brother.
How did you find this place?
How is my father?
Boran Bey.
My Shahzade.
This time we made a big plan.
I will tell you everything now.
Now listen to me carefully.
I will surrender to Ulugan
to save my people from...
...the poison and the Mongols.
What are you saying, my Bey?
My Bala... We need to do this.
I will do this for the
state and for my people...
...I spent my years for.
Don't worry. My lineage will continue. My
children and grandchildren will follow me.
They will all follow us.
Our state will exist forever.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
They are keeping Orhan at Cam Valley, right?
My Bey, even though those
dogs covered my eyes...
...I kept the rivers and
the rocky roads in my mind.
They are keeping my Shahzade at Cam Valley.
Now..
...I will take the antidote from Ulugan...
...and surrender to him.
And he will probably take me to
the capital city of Sogut or Yenisehir.
What about my brother?
You will raid the Mongol
headquarters after me and take Orhan.
And in that time..
...the people will have healed.
But the actual duty...
...belongs to Samil.
You will come after me.
You will attack Ulugan in Sogut or Yenisehir...
...when he least expects it.
As you order, my Bey.
I will kill that infidel before anyone sees me.
My Bey, why don't we
kill that dog in our tribe...
..when he is on the way here?
No, I cannot risk my people's lives.
First, they will take the antidote and
they will heal. We need to know this.
Okay, my Bey.
And you, after taking Orhan,
will come to me with horsemen.
-As you order my Bey.
Beys
Brothers!
We are going to Sogut!
We will make these Mongol dogs
regret that they have stepped on our lands.
Allah is the Greatest!
You cannot do this!
Come on Osman.
Start speaking.
Tell them that you bowed down to Mongols.
Then kneel.
Why don't you speak? Come on!
Samil... What are you trying to do, Osman?
Or people...
I hear those who say "Osman Bey...
...gave up his state for our lives.'
I hear them.
You should know..
I never gave up on my people...
...or our state which we
established with all those sufferings.
Is that so?
Do you think everything is over
because you have the antidote?
But you are wrong.
We will never stop before Ulugan dog dies!
Now!
We better leave, Lukas.
Come on.
Don't kill him! I have a better plan for him!
So this was all a game, Osman?
You wanted to set a trap and kill me...
-What did you think?
What did you think, you dog?
Did you think I'd bow down to you?
I will not kill you Osman.
I will not kill you.
I will kill your child Orhan in front of
you as a price for what you've done.
The spy that Osman placed in your castle.
Was his name Ilbay?
He was the one who saved Ulugan's life.
I saw him.
Ilbay?
We will learn, Sofia.
We will learn what they are trying to do.
Commander Ulugan, Turks raided our headquarters.
They took Orhan from us.
He really is his father's son.
So you saved your son, huh, Osman?
So?
What will happen to your Hatun?
What will happen to your children and people?
Who will save them from my hands?
I will...
I will drown you in your own blood... I will...
...cut you into pieces. Into pieces!
You heard, Altuga.
Kill everyone in the Kayi tribe!
Nokers (Mongolian Soldier)!
Let go!
Do you think this will stop me?
Don't worry!
Allah is with us!
The antidote is showing
its effect, thanks to Allah.
The patients in the healing
tent also started getting up.
Thanks to Allah.
The poison lost its effect, huh?
Thanks to Allah...
But...
...I keep seeing my father
whenever I close my eyes, mother.
For our lives..
Your lives, our people's lives...
...mean the well-being and
future of our state, my daughter.
If that's what our Osman
Bey deemed appropriate...
..then this is what we must do.
Still, I cannot wait here.
I am alright now! I will question those Mongols!
Stop...
My Allah... He is not even a meter
long, but he says he will question them...
Ghazi...
You have a duty here.
Who will protect us if you leave?
True.
Besides, our Shahzade's child is also here.
We cannot leave.
When Orhan comes back, I will
tell him about your heroism, Ghazi.
Swear?
Oh no!
We are done..
Now, he will keep talking about himself.
Now we will unite and resist.
We will protect each other and our people.
We will get over this trouble
together with Allah's permission.
-My Orhan and my Osman will come.
-They will come.
-We will ruin the games of those demons.
-God willing.
Osman Bey...
...won't give up easily.
He must have a plan, right,Bala Hatun?
Come, Meryem.
If the cruel have a plan...
...we also have one, my daughter.
Everything will be alright, God willing.
Are you feeling better?
I am.
Thanks to you.
Meryem.
You kept saying "Aunt when you were sick.
Do you have an aunt who lives far away?
Aunt?
...didn't have anyone..
...except for my grandmother, Bala Hatun.
Did I really say "aunt"
Yes.
But I guess you said that because of your fever.
Samil, what are you doing here?
-My Shahzade...
The situation is not good...
What happened Samil? Tell me!
Someone attacked me when I
was about to kill Ulugan, Orhan Bey...
I failed.
Who, brother? Tell me! Who?
I couldn't see his face..
...but he knew we'd kill Ulugan.
I barely saved my life to let you know.
Samil...
...is my father alright? Is he alright?
-He was, but...
Ulugan took an oath for revenge.
Nokers (Mongolian Soldier)
came and told him that you were abducted.
Now he is going to our tribe.
He said he would burn it down.
To the tribe! Now!
Ilbay...
Let's see what you are going to do now.
Move! Move!
I cannot help it anymore Ayse.
I will punish those Mongol dogs.
Alps' swords might be
taken, but I have mine here.
Ghazi stop!
Don't go!
Burn the tents Nokers(Mongolian Soldier)!
Don't show mercy!
-Mongols!
Meryem, take the children, go inside!
Hatuns! Attack!
Hang on Alps! Hang on!
We will send these dogs
away from our tribe! Come on!
Osman's Hatun!
Your family and people, for
whom you have chained yourself...
...to save their lives now
await death at the edge.
When we go there, I'll just look at your face.
When you are looking at the heads of
your Hatun, your children, your family...
..all of them..
I will just look at the
growing fire in your eyes.
Look at me, if you do
something bad to my family or...
...my people, I will fill your
eye sockets with blood.
Once I get rid of my chains...
Once I get rid of my chains, then you'll see.
Then you'll see.
I just care about who will rule
and who will die in Kayi tribe now.
Now think about what you'll see in your tribe.
Attack, alps!
Attack, Sisters!
Shed the blood of demons!
Fatma!
Meryem. Meryem.
Come on, come on.
Orhan.
Come to me.
Fight, warriors!
Come on! Come on!
Alps, show no mercy for those jackals!
Come on!
My Shahzade, watch out!
I won't let them win even if I have no hands!
Come on, warriors!
Holofira, Holofira.
Orhan, are you alright?
Your hand. What did they do to you?
-I'm fine.
I'll be good. Come on.
Everybody will get what they deserve.
This chair belongs to me now.
I will rule this state now, Osman.
I said you were strong.
I knew you would come.
You didn't prove me to be wrong, Begum Hatun.
Do you know what I will do next?
I do.
I saw this in my dream.
You will accept my offer.
You will be my wife.
Wife of Ilbay Bey,
...grandson of Sungur Tegin.
We will rule this state together.
Your dream was a good sign then.
I will marry you, Ilbay.
Look at those people...
...who take shelter under
the shadow of your tent.
They will all die because of your arrogance.
Even the bravest person will be
surprised by what I'm going to do to you.
Don't harm my tribe and people.
Kill me.
I won't kill you once but a thousand times.
You think you're in an oasis
in the hell pit you've fallen into.
I will take your head before
the blood in the tribe dries up.
Enough.
Don't you want to know who
died and who lives in your family?
If you have harmed a single one in my family,
..I will eat you this dark soil.
I will make birds and worms eat you.
Your people will be eaten by birds and worms.
They will eat their flesh and bones!
Then I will hold a feast in your tent.
Well... Let's not make birds and worms starve.
Move.
Cerkutay!
This is the end of Turks
you have become a dog for!
It's the day I will put a
leash around your neck!
Father, I'm here!
-I'm here, father!
-Ghazi.
Ghazi.
Ghazi, go away!
He takes after you.
-Father.
-I'll kill you and make him a noker for me.
Ghazi, go. Go! Go!
-Father, no!
Bala Hatun...
Alaaddin Bey!
My Shahzade! They are
too many. We're losing this.
Boran Bey, we have to leave
immediately. We can't hold anymore.
Take women and children away quickly! Come on!
Bala Hatun. Shahzade Alaaddin says
we should leave the tribe immediately.
-We'll take elders, women and children away.
-We're losing it, Boran.
They are too many. There is nothing to do.
Come on, come on!
Gonca!
You take the elders. Holofira
you gather the children.
Ulgen, sisters... We'll protect our people.
We'll get out of here alive.
Come on
Come on!
Brother! Brother!
Mother is taking people away. We have to leave!
-We can't stand anymore. We have to go!
-We aren't going anywhere!
Anywhere! I won't leave the tribe!
-Even at the cost of my life!
-Brother!
Come on! Come on!
My Shahzade, they destroyed our tribe!
They killed people! We have to go!
I won't leave my tribe to
those dastards! Come on!
Come on! Come on, warriors!
Hurry up! Go towards the woods!
Fatma! Fatma, hold her.
Hurry up! Run towards the woods!
Come on, come on. Go towards the woods.
No, I can't go.
-I will make them pay for this!
-Ghazi, stop.
Die, you heathens!
Get off!
-Ghazi?
-Get off!
Come on, faster!
Leave me, dastard!
What have you done, Ghazi?
My Shahzade. We need to go.
-The tribe has fallen.
-I won't leave!
My Shahzade. My Shahzade, we have to go.
-My Shahzade.
-Boran, leave me!
My Shahzade! It's over! It's over!
It's over, my Shahzade.
It's over, my Shahzade. Don't you
see? Remember what our Bey said.
For our state to live forever, you have to live.
The land might be lost, but
the tradition remains, Orhan Bey.
Brother, we have to go now. Boran Bey is right.
The land might be lost, but
the tradition remains. Come on.
Come on!
Come on! -We are going back!
Come on Alps!
Come on!
This is the end, Yusuf...
We will come back for sure. For sure.
Brother..
Come on brother.
What..
What...
...did you do to my tribe...
...to my people...
...to my sons...
...to my children?
You faithless dogs!
What did you do?
How could you hurt them?!
What did they do to you?!
My tent...
You killed my people, my innocent people.
Faithless dogs!
Faithless dog!
Ulugan!
Come! Face me! Come on!
Come on!
Face me! Come on!
Ulugan!
Let go! Let go!
You are done, Osman!
Your state is destroyed Your tradition...
Your state is destroyed!
Your tradition...
...your banner, they are all under my feet now!
The Sky Wolf Osman is destroyed now!
You no longer exist!
You did this to my state and to my people...
If I don't punish you for this...
...then may the blood of all
our martyrs be haram to me!
I will shed dark blood with dark steel...
...and water the dark soil with your blood!
May it come in clean and
come out covered in blood!
If I do not take an eye for
an eye, a tooth for a tooth...
...a life for a life..
...then may they not call me Osman Bey!